{"data":[{"question":"How many pints are there in two quarts?' 'There are _______ pints.'","a":"four","b":"two","c":"six","d":"eight","answer":"1","explain":"\n-1 US pint = 473.176473 milliliters \n-1 US quart = 946.352946 milliliters ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"That is a ________.","a":"five-gallons tank","b":"five-gallon tank","c":"tank of five gallon","d":"five-gallons-tank","answer":"2","explain":"-Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular)\n\n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Mum, ______ are you?","a":"how heavy","b":"what heavy","c":"how weight","d":"how much weigh","answer":"1","explain":"\n- How heavy: how much does it weigh","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"He was run over by a _______ truck.","a":"ton three","b":"three-ton","c":"three-tons","d":"three tons","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"You are gaining ______.","a":"weigh","b":"weighs","c":"weight","d":"weights","answer":"3","explain":"- Gain weight: increase weight","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"Mrs Jones, our English teacher, weighs 10 ______ 6 lbs.","a":"stones","b":"stone","c":"quarter","d":"kilograms","answer":"2","explain":"- 1 stone = 6.35029318 kilograms\u00a0\n- The plural form of stone is correctly stone","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"This truck can carry about five tons. Yes, it's a _______.","a":"five-ton truck","b":"five tons truck","c":"truck of five tond","d":"five-tons-truck","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Compound Adjectives with Numbers: number+ name of thing (in singular) \n- Usually, hyphens are used to link the words together to show that it is one adjective ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"An English pound has _______ ounces.","a":"8","b":"6","c":"16","d":"14","answer":"3","explain":"\n-1 pound = 453.59237 grams \n-1 ounce = 28.3495231 grams ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"________ is that old trunk?","a":"What weight","b":"What heavy","c":"How weight","d":"How heavy","answer":"4","explain":"\n- How heavy: how much does it weigh ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"},{"question":"In England an average-sized man weighs about ______ stone.","a":"100","b":"12","c":"150","d":"6","answer":"2","explain":"- A stone: equal to 6.35 kilograms\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"71","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"1"}]}